Kateryna Butsnieva

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

(512) 888-4419



butsnieva@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/butsnieva



butsnieva.dev



github.com/butsnieva





Education and Certifications

The University of Texas

Coding bootcamp Sep 2021

SI Computer School

"QA Professional" course Jul 2019

Prydniprovsk State Academy of Civil Architecture and Engineering

Completed coursework towards Bachelor Architecture and Design, 2016

Computer Academy "STEP"

Software Development. Software Engineering Dec 2014

Technical skills

Languages: HTML, CSS,

JavaScript

Database Management: MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose Libraries/Frameworks: ¡Query, React.js, Express.js, Bootstrap, UiKit, Tailwind

Other Technologies: Node.js, Socket.io, Handlebars, Git, Bash, Selenium, webdriver.io

Summary

Ambitious Full Stack Web Developer, effective at using the latest technologies to create efficient and maintainable back-end interfaces and approachable user experiences.

Brings 4+ years of professional experience in QA Testing, ability to design and develop web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases. Self-motivated, able to grasp concepts quickly with minimal supervision, take ownership of problems and follow them through to completion.

Experience

QA Engineer

SI Global Solutions | Austin, TX | Mar, 2019 - Current

- Performed Exploratory testing, Functional, Ad-hoc, Usability, Smoke testing, API testing, Regression, and Database validation testing
- Involved in all Agile ceremonies such as planning, stand up, grooming, retrospective.
- Used SQL Queries consistently to verify the data from SQL server database and Back end testing
- Involved in Mobile Web and Native Mobile APP testing on Android, iPad and iPhone, Emulator, Simulator to perform functional, usability, compatibility
- Created and maintained automated regression test scripts using Selenium WebDriver with JavaScript webdriver.io. Chai and Mocha frameworks

QA Analyst II

B.WELL | Austin, TX | Oct, 2020 - Mar, 2021

- Developed and maintained quality assurance procedure documentation.
- Developed test scripts utilizing comprehensive business requirements, functional documentation and processes.

Chief Operation Officer (2,5y), <- Sales Manager (9mo)

Global Trans USA | Austin, TX | Jan, 2017 - Jan, 2020

- Mentor and interact with members of staff at all levels.
- Creating, improving, implementing, and enforcing policies and procedures of the organization that will improve operational and financial effectiveness of the company.
- Evaluation of potential mergers, acquisitions, and partnerships.

Manual QA Tester

"CITRUS" Online Gadget Store | Odessa, Ukraine | Feb, 2014 - Mar, 2016

- Documented test reports and defect reports and presenting the conclusions to the team.
- Participated in the defect review board meetings and weekly team meetings to give and get status updates on the working objectives.